Junior Web Developer ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99 Email: info@qwikresume.com Website: www.gwikresume.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/qwikresume Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama.

Objective

Junior Web Developer with 3 plus years of experience able to build .Net web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery and maintenance. Extremely passionate towards software architecture and design combined with sensitivity to serve the needs of the business balanced with the delivery of high quality solutions.

Skills

.NET, ASP, ASP.NET, Database, MS ASP, JQuery, Javascript, SQL, Visual Studio, Visual Basic, C#, Angular JS, Bootstrap, MVC, Web Services, CSS3, HTML 5, HTML, Entity Framework, Databases

Work Experience

Junior Web Developer

Bahwan Cybertek - May 2016 - Present

- Designed and implemented internal and client solutions by using Visual Studio 2013, SQL server 2012.
- Creating models within an MVC application that implements the business logic necessary to satisfy business requirements. The module also describes how to implement a connection to a database using the entity framework and LinQ.
- Implementing advanced search, paging, and export functionality for each screen.
- Using jQuery JSON for the dynamic user interface, retrieval, and posting of data.
- Implementing web services for communicating one application to another application by using SOAP.
- Implementing WSDL XML document to locate and describe the web services.
- Worked in Asp.Net security mechanisms such as impersonation, authentication and authorization.

Junior Web Developer

ABC Corp - 2015 - 2016

- Worked with an agile team to develop, test, and maintain web-based business applications built on Microsoft technologies.
- Assisted in the collection and documentation of users requirements, development of user stories, and estimates.
- Designed, developed, and unit tested the applications in accordance with established standards
- Participated in the peer-reviews of solution designs and related code.
- Packaged and supported the deployment of releases.
- Analyzed and resolved the technical and application problems.
- Adhered to the high-quality development principles while delivering solutions on-time and onbudget)

Education	
Master Of Science - July 2014 to December 2015(University Of Central Missouri - Wa MO)Computer Science - (College Of Health)	rrensburg,